export const Questions = [
    {prompt: "How do you say 'Good Morning'?", optionA: "E ka bo", optionB: "E ka san", optionC: "E ka ro", optionD: "e ka leh", answer: "C",},
    {prompt: "What does Kele n Sele'? mean", optionA: "What is happening", optionB: "How old are you?", optionC: "How are things?", optionD: "What poppin?", answer: "A",},
    {prompt: "How do you say 'Good Evening'?", optionA: "E ka bo", optionB: "E ka san", optionC: "E ka ro", optionD: "e ka leh", answer: "D",},
    {prompt: "What does 'Ba Wa Ni' mean in English?", optionA: "How are things?", optionB: "Hi there", optionC: "Good Night", optionD: "Do you want to hang out", answer: "A",},
    {prompt: "Translate 'E ka ro'", optionA: "Good evening", optionB: "Good Morning", optionC: "Good Night", optionD: "Welcome", answer: "B",},
    {prompt: "Translate 'E ka saan'", optionA: "Good evening", optionB: "Good Morning", optionC: "Good Afternoon", optionD: "Good Night", answer: "C",},
    {prompt: "Translate 'E ka leh'", optionA: "Good evening", optionB: "Good Morning", optionC: "Good Afternoon", optionD: "Good Night", answer: "A",},
    {prompt: "How do you say ' O da ro'?", optionA: "Good evening", optionB: "Good Morning", optionC: "Good Afternoon", optionD: "Good Night", answer: "D",},
    {prompt: "How do you say 'are you good'?", optionA: "kilo n sele", optionB: "Ba Wo Ni", optionC: "So Wa Dada", optionD: "Odola", answer: "C",},
    {prompt: "How do you say 'til tomorrow'?", optionA: "kilo n sele", optionB: "Ba Wo Ni", optionC: "So Wa Dada", optionD: "Odola", answer: "D",},
]